I chose the University of Halmstad because it is close to my family members-
-Personally, I like a little smaller schools when you get the family feeling.
The best thing about my education is the ability to learn one-
-Sid range of these technical modules.
And then I refer to electronics, mechanics and computer science.
I have been able to be in Germany as an exchange student.
With the help of Halmstad University, they have helped me with an internship there.
So I have made an exchange half-spring-
-and six months as a trainee there.
I would like to work in the industry.
After doing my internship in Germany, I will now also read my master there.